I want to tell you first
The correct expression about the origin of this theory (I think)
Back in the early 1980s,
I was about the same age as you now
There was a trend of thought that existed, especially around 1984
Every generation has its own worries about reality or imagined reality
Our generation
The main concern is nuclear war
(You know) it started at a certain point and lasted for many years
Real worries
I used to go to Arizona
Visit the intercontinental ballistic missile, a decommissioned
Intercontinental nuclear missile
And the missile silo, which is very large, and the rocket is from
Launched here
They can fly half a circle around the earth
It’s very deep underground, in a very thick iron gate
Is a soft pale green
Like the color that people liked in the 50s
It's like a light green Star Trek console
what
So we get down to
Fangting, located in the desert, outside the Fangting
how to say
There is a magical object
I don't have a better word to describe
Is the front cone of the missile,
Very big
Very high, the top is like the top of a bullet
About three-quarters of an inch thick,
A bit like resin plastic.
This design is to protect the missile from melting when returning.
It stands there
It is inevitable that it is thought-provoking,
See here for the time being
Then we went again
Missile silos,
Interestingly
Since the Reagan era was retired, the front of the missile well
Became a museum,
The collection includes handicrafts from the 1980s,
Reagan and Barbachev met several times during this period.
The staff working in the museum are from the southern United States,
They are probably the age of (your) grandparents
Very friendly
And they love it here,
(This feeling) is like visiting grandmother’s nuclear silo
So there is a sense of conflict, you know this place
It used to be unknown, but now it is connected with hospitality
Very surreal in this dimension
Anyway, we entered
Inside the silo
They performed a mock launch for us
Let's imagine
A metal panel that is twice as long as this, and another thing like this 16 feet away
Use upgraded 50s technology
Imagine what you have to do to launch it
There are two people each with a key hanging around their necks
Although I don’t think the key will be kept on their neck forever
In order to start the launch, for safety reasons,
These two must be the two keys at the same time,
Put it in the lock and keep it for 10 seconds,
Only missiles can be launched. Of course, missiles are not as big as rockets launched to the moon.
But it’s still quite big. You know that the light silo can easily make this classroom wider.
And many times higher than the classroom.
The surreal simulation launch they showed us,
Because someone asked, they also told us one thing,
There used to be only one key,
But don't tell us when
Maybe during the Cuban Missile Crisis
Because we're almost
Maybe more than a little worse
It seems that in 1984,
There has been another crisis peak
This year there is a famous movie called
After the catastrophe
This movie won at the time
More reviews than any other movie,
There was also a saying
After the aftermath of the nuclear war, the survivors
All very realistic
And are all too scared,
I later found out
This film is a reason for Reagan’s pressure to restart negotiations with the Soviet Union
It depends on what you think
this movie
Then everyone sees it, 5 years later
No one foresaw the collapse of the Soviet Union
And in fact, 1989 did not disintegrate in a sense
Such a huge machine
Will not disintegrate all at once, but slowly dissolve over time,
Sometimes it is faltering and unable to support
It’s like losing faith in their creed
On the bright side,
Russia’s Soviet system,
Is a collection of multiple provinces,
Like an empire,
China and North Korea's current system
It still exists after the Cold War.
There are also such systems in Southeast Asia and Africa.
Are based on Marxist hypotheses,
The hypothesis holds that utopia exists
And suppose that in the future utopia,
Property is shared, everyone
Have enough
Everyone can do what they are good at as needed,
This is a wonderful view, you can imagine
It will be very attractive
Even if rationally,
Because all other systems have
Huge income gap
Just like the laws of nature govern
You can even model this with Pareto distribution
Pareto distribution is like this,
It is different from the normal distribution, as you have known before.
Despite many things
Are in line with the normal distribution, but the normal distribution still has its
Not applicable
If you have played Monopoly, you understand
What is the Pareto distribution,
Assuming everyone has at the beginning
The same amount of money,
Can be understood as property, the same amount of property,
Then as the game progresses, like a chance function
I mean, I know you are using strategy in this game,
But the basic rule is to buy everything you can get
Then stingy deals
At the beginning everyone has the same amount of property
Then you start the game
If there are a sufficient number of players theoretically a normal distribution
Because some people will keep winning relatively,
While others will keep losing
Money began to show a normal distribution
but
About money and many other things
0 will get involved
0 is a strange number,
If you play a trading game and the asset is 0
You are out.
So it is very difficult to recover from 0,
Just like if you are cursed in the Monopoly game,
You have some resources when you start
But when you enter certain hotels, there is a crisis,
You will be swept out
At this time, your assets are 0, even if you have something
If you are lucky, maybe you will be saved
But you know when bad luck comes
So what happens when you keep playing Monopoly
More and more people have property 0
Fewer and fewer people have more and more
assets
When the game is over,
Everyone has become a pauper, only one person has all the assets
The interesting phenomenon revealed in this is
In a sense, this is how the trading game works
You may want to know why the rich and poor are uneven in society
It is easy to think of social corruption,
Maybe
Society is a bit or very corrupt,
This has changed,
There is no society without crime,
This is inherent composition
In short,
Trading games have a tendency to produce Pareto distribution, that is, most people have very little wealth.
Very few people have a lot of wealth
This ratio is about 1%, yes
The number 1% is observed in every society
It has nothing to do with what kind of government or system,
This situation must have happened in the Soviet regime,
Many people die because of extreme poverty
and so
Utopian dream
It’s impossible for many very complicated reasons
One of them is that when people are trading, it is difficult to
(Inherent) statistical distribution
Because it’s just a statistical law, and I should tell you
Pareto distribution also dominates many situations,
So, taking the book market as an example, if I remember correctly,
About a million English books were published last year,
About 500 of them sold more than 100,000 copies,
There are many other sets of books sold 0 copies,
Among these 500 books, one of them is authored by Stephen King,
He can take about half of the sales,
Because there are about 5 writers in English books
In each airport’s paper media shelves,
All occupy the most conspicuous position,
(This position) is very valuable, yes, this kind of information is repeated everywhere
And the location is outstanding,
If people are in a hurry and just want to find something to read, they won’t care about the name
Just grab a copy directly from a conspicuous position, so most of the money goes into these people’s pockets, you know,
Success breeds success,
Failure breeds failure, this curve need not be linear,
This is a difficult situation
Especially in society,
What we know is
Extend this unfairness
People at the bottom of the Pareto distribution
Will become more and more aggressive,
It’s like, you can think that men have a threshold for violent behavior
This situation is important for men
But not important for women
This is actually a different state for men and women
Because men as women’s partners are market-oriented to a certain extent,
So this is important for men
Men compete with each other in an unequal society
Corresponding social status
If you are in a lower position in society
Basically no chance to rise
Because society is not structured
So men are motivated
Become more aggressive
And showing criminal tendencies
You can think of a crime threshold
In specific areas such as geography or politics,
More unfair pressure
More pressure
The more men commit crimes above the threshold
There is a lot of research in drug gangs
Especially in the Chicago study, a sociologist even went directly into the drug gang
Maybe the leader of a drug gang,
It cannot be said that narcissism is inevitable, but it may be a reasonable way to explain the problem
Maybe he
Feel complacent about the idea of ​​being the subject of a book
So this sociologist can
Get in touch with the drug gang and have a considerable degree of understanding
Then the housing plan in the drug gang area
Caused their residence to be demolished and the gang fell apart
Sociologists got those books
Because they keep
He found ordinary street drug dealers,
They have to find a job first
Income is well below average
At the top of the gang
According to the Pareto distribution, a small percentage of people at the top earn a lot of income
Bottom
Wait for the opportunity to see if they have the opportunity to upgrade
This is quite a violent game
Maybe some people are out at the top
It will open up some opportunities to people at the lower levels
Maybe someone can level up
So Pareto distribution is reflected in different fields
Such as on the bestseller list
This distribution also applies to all areas of human production
Whether in creative fields such as art or industrial products
Almost all failures
Few successes
Beyond anyone's knowledge
Take Apple as an example
They have competitors
But they have an absolute advantage, earning huge income of billions of dollars
I don’t know that Apple’s market value is trillions of dollars
Very close even if not
This is a lot of money
If I remember correctly, the 40 richest people in the world
Has as many assets as the bottom 2 billion people
It’s not that they stuffed the mattress with money
Or they have skyscrapers full of money
The money has lost its economic value
You can't spend 28 billion dollars
So sometimes you can do something good with him, such as Bill Gates
Use the money reasonably
The reason for talking about the above is that you should know
Unfairness
Permeate all aspects of human life
It's just like
Scoring in a hockey game, my son told me
He has stable scoring statistics on the hockey team
If you don’t count Wayne’s score,
He still gets enough points as an assist, more than any other hockey player
and so
Even at the top of the Pareto distribution
Some people do what they are good at
There are other people who do better than these people, even unmatched
A lot of profits will flow to these places, and you know why this is so
Like you start writing a book
In rare cases, some people read your book and they like it
You have a higher probability of writing a book
If the reader still likes it, then you will publish a third book, and then the reader will start to understand who you are,
Because they know you, they will give you some opportunities and your social network will grow
Your wealth and creativity
Will grow exponentially
On the other hand
If you start to fail, why some people fail,
A popular idea in our culture is that lack of money leads to poverty. This is a stupid idea.
Because money is difficult to control, I have a client who is a drug addict
The worst for them is that they have some money
They are over, first of all, they are gathered around
Some people with antisocial personality tendencies
Especially people who are not optimistic enough to protect themselves well
Once they have money, they will go to the bar and spend money with friends.
I was particularly impressed with one person, whenever he has money,
He will be missing for 5 days, you may find him in the ditch, he will go to the bar,
Spend every penny on drugs and alcohol
Wake up in the ditch, dying
Then he will be ashamed, horrified, and regret
Then he will regroup until the next check appears
Then the same thing happened again
It seems that money is not good for everyone
It’s difficult to manage money well, and money is easy to lose. I mean, the elderly have a lot of time
Scammers covet them online all the time
Just giving money is like pouring water on their hands
This will not have a great effect
Of course, giving money to the poor with low IQ is not very useful
People don’t like the concept of IQ
Because it seems very arbitrary,
Feel unworthy of having a high IQ
Actually IQ was set at the beginning and it is very stable
You can keep people with high IQs from being educated, make them stupid, and cannot release their own possibilities
but
If anyone can improve the IQ of people with low IQ,
You can definitely apply for the Nobel Prize, because people have tried all kinds of things
The most recent ones are related to the people of lumosity games,
This game can live forever anything except from being smart
We don't know why
Intelligence is a cross-domain phenomenon
You can practice in any field until you become proficient
And hope that this will make you more comfortable in other fields
Not actually
So far no one can do it, even if someone claims to be rentable, it turns out to be untenable in the end
People have tried for a long time and still can’t do it
Different IQs do make a difference
Your average IQ is about 125, 130
115 has exceeded 85% of the population
But 115 is still not enough for going to a prestigious university
130 may be able to make you learn something when you graduate
145 is the top level
You can do whatever you want
The higher your IQ, the greater the difference in abilities in different aspects
For example, you have a very high IQ in language, but not necessarily in mathematics, or other aspects
But high IQ is still a significant factor in success
I don't know how to do this
Why people with high IQ can make more money
Because of higher production efficiency
If you sort 1000 people by IQ, people with high IQ will first come up with new ways
They will also generate more solutions and evaluate which is better
People with an IQ of 90 account for 15% of the total population
Think about it carefully, it accounts for 15% of the total population
This is just a threshold for being able to read the instructions and follow the instructions
Our society is becoming increasingly complex
It is clear
You know what liberals think
Social injustice is caused by unemployment
Conservatives believe that everyone should have a shared job
But neither side has thought that the gap between human intelligence and ability is so large
Bigger than anyone thought
This leads to a structural problem
I have a client
I found him a volunteer job, which is harder to obtain than expected
You need a certificate of no criminal record
Sometimes volunteer work is harder than real work
But we still helped him get this job
he needs
Fold up papers or documents, etc. He works in a charity
He needs to fold these documents three times so that they can fit in an envelope
Files are piled up into mountains, and you need to match them with the right envelope
The envelopes are piled up, some are in French and some are in English
The French envelope must match the French document
If there is an envelope out of order
He must figure out which document matches
then
Some documents also have photos or pictures attached
These cannot be bent
And they haven’t put them in one place, so we have to find a way to see how to fold the files
Each situation folds in a different way
Another thing is
I never realized how difficult it is to fold the documents into an envelope
Until i saw someone couldn't do it
He may have an IQ of about 80
If you meet him on the street, you won’t notice the difference
He is just an ordinary person
Can't see what's wrong
I was trained to stack these files for about 30 hours
He did quite well
If you are good at doing this
When folded
The edges must be very precise
The error cannot exceed 1/2 mm
Then fold a second time
The error is the same as the first time
Assuming the error is 1/8 inch when first folded
The same goes for the second fold
It will be a bit deformed, which means the total error is 1/4 inch
Then I can’t put the envelope
The envelope will be crumpled and then jammed in the sorting machine
He tried his best to do this job well
But the agency still absolutely fired him
This means
You can't find a job
Even a voluntary charity job
Still decided to fire you
You understand what i mean
I communicated with the lady who runs this charity
Explain that the loss of this job may be fatal to everyone
Of course she also has her consideration
He often asks others how to do his job well
This will affect the efficiency of others
This is a real conflict, it’s not that she is mean
She wants to ensure the normal operation of the organization
This put her in a dilemma
Soon after this, he finally decided that this job was not suitable for him,
This is stressful
He gave up and the problem was finally solved, except that he still had no job is a problem
Fortunately, this story ended well
As far as I know, he has a dog because he is very lonely.
He trained this dog
Lost 30 pounds
Because the dog is in a dominant position at the beginning
He must fight with the dog to decide who has control. Keeping a dog has many responsibilities
He has a deep relationship with the dog
Think of ways to live with the dog
It sounds weird, like a nuclear bomb launching bin. At first, people gathered around him.
Because he felt he was abusing the dog
Actually what I saw was that the dog was abusing him
later
He got a job training a dog for a lady
Hurray!!!
It's a miracle
Anyway, I tell this story because
There was a reason for the Cold War
The reason is
unfair
There are different theories attributing unfairness
For example, why does unfairness exist?
Marx theorizes
Human property should be average,
Some people grab more property from other people
It’s easy to rule out this concept because the total amount of money is not fixed
Because of inflation, our technology has become proficient
Many people are trapped by money because they have a lot of wealth
For example, Bill Gates, who popularized computing and made computing possible for everyone
This looks good to him
The other person is steve Jobs (Apple founder)
And Elon Musk (paypal, founder of tesla)
These people can control a lot of resources
but
This is not just lying in the money pile
They want to continue to do things, use the money to do things
In short
Russia uses Marxism to guide
Try to
Average wealth gap
It's not an exaggeration to say it's a rare disaster
Many people here don’t understand this for various reasons
People will not be taught about this issue
But in fact, there are statistics that estimate that more than 30 million people were killed in Russia between 1919 and 1959.
It's cruel
Many people died of starvation
I saw a photo the other day and I posted it on Tweet
This is the worst photo I have ever seen, it contains a lot of information
I have seen many terrible photos before
Because I have done a lot of investigations related to totalitarianism
This photo was taken in the early days of the famine
During Soviet rule, about 3 million people died
This photo shows a rural couple
Selling a human body divided into pieces behind a table in the market
I have a quirk
I don’t think it’s good for me
But it helps me understand things better
When I see some people do some extreme things
I realized that this happened many years ago when I was working in a high-level security prison
I tried to imagine when I was in a situation
I would do something like this
Trust me
This is a terrible thing because
Actually very likely
No matter what kind of people you have read about doing unimaginable things, you think you would never do it
It's actually possible
Imagine you are in that situation
This is very helpful for you to understand this phenomenon
Because for the things you don't want to know
Necessary for this kind of inspiration
Imagine yourself as a criminal
It will make you understand this world, make you understand human nature
At the same time you have to endure a lot
In a very structured society, such as Canada
People are calm
Because our heater is always heating
Always have electricity
There are pipes, it’s a miracle, they have been working normally
By imagining the completion of this project, I remind myself every day that this is a miracle
Very cold outside
Cannot grow any crops
Stand outside for 24 hours and you will freeze to death
If any public infrastructure is unreliable at any time, we will be in serious trouble
But they have never been unreliable
It's impossible
Because of the reliable public infrastructure
We don’t need to compete fiercely with each other
That means you don’t have to do it for food
Fierce competition for housing
It's easy to think that you are a good person
Because you never do bad things to other people
Ironically because you never need to do bad things, there is no reason to do bad things
These reasons have actually risen many times in the past
Actually this is an axiom, no exceptions
The reason we are exceptional is because
Complete social facilities and systems
It seems to me a little hard to understand that he will exist
In short
Back to the industrial age, after the end of the industrial revolution
The working environment of workers is quite cruel
George Orwell wrote a book called Road to Wigan Pier
Describes things in the 1930s
I guess it should be in the 30s
Working and living in the mines of this England
These poor workers
They have to climb two miles in the tunnel to get to work. They cannot stand in the tunnel
Then work for 8 hours to chisel coal
It's difficult, dirty and dangerous
Of course there is black lung disease, and the income is not high
After work
Climb two more miles back
No reward for climbing the tunnel back and forth, just commuting
The residence of these people
It’s not good, and the food is not good. Many people lose their teeth when they are about 30 years old.
Even in the UK, being poor is not a joke, of course there are many rich people here
So there are enough reasons
Think that the uneven distribution of rich and poor is a natural state
In the west, in 1895, per capita daily consumption was equivalent to today’s $1
This is not common in most places in the world today
So there are reasons to consider inequality
Russia is inspired by Marxism, we are inspired by John Mueller and John Locke
British classic democracy
After 70 years of improvement
This theory now seems very applicable
But if you consider (damn) competition
The bottom of this concept will be very different
These two thoughts have confronted and conflicted, and they have not completely ended yet.
For example, China, although it is now a mixture of communism and capitalism
I hope they are more interested in becoming rich
Greed is the main driving force of war
During the 1989 incident
Showed that the Soviet system was not fully functional
Even in large stores in Moscow, there are not enough consumer goods
People seem to be losing faith
For a while, I don’t know if you have heard of the Dallas show
This is a soap opera that airs at night
About some of the top 1% richest Texans
This drama is very popular in East Germany
The air time is empty
When sitting on the platform of a Soviet-style building
You must also fight against the relatives you provide information
Because at that time one-third of the people in East Germany were government intelligence agents
Watching the Dallas show is ideologically incorrect
Feel split
There was still a small-scale war in Eastern Europe
But it fell apart in an incredibly peaceful way and became what Germany is now.
I don’t know if this is related to the Soviets
at least
There is no evidence that they are mortal enemies
The world is getting better
Except everyone tells you their status is still 40 years ago
But also better than 50 years ago
Many people have been lifted out of poverty in the past 15 years
There have been cases in history where people gathered economic resources
Want to achieve high growth that the most optimistic cannot predict
It’s not that we don’t have any problems
During this period
I am addicted to
One question, this question is
why
Humans have to develop two camps
Produce a lot of hydrogen bombs
I don’t know if you understand hydrogen bombs, they need to be ejected by atoms
The atomic bomb is already very powerful,
The hydrogen bomb is more powerful
At the height of the cold war
Thousands of these weapons are directed at the Soviet Union and the West
This is enough
Destroy everything
This is a very dangerous game
Whether for human purpose or accident
It’s a mistake, or yo people are a bit crazier than expected
Maybe you would say no one wants to really destroy the world
This shows that you don’t know enough about Stalin
All people who lived in power in the 20th century under Stalin’s statistics
Stalin is
Often bring things to destruction
There is a saying that he was murdered by Khrushchev and his staff
Khrushchev is the next generation of leaders
If he was not murdered, at least no medical care was provided when he was sick
There is reasonable evidence that he wanted to invade Western Europe
He doesn't care how much damage it will cause
He has persecuted millions
It won't bother him
This is just my guess, it's crazy when I do this
So I started thinking about the belief system
Because each camp has its own belief system, the Western system was born in Greece/Rome/Jesus/Christ and has
Very long history
Also produced in different philosophical systems and inspired by them
The Soviet system is based on rational philosophy and IQ
Contrary to the West
Each system builds a society according to its ideas
I have been involved in political science for quite some time
Political scientists and economists agree
People compete for resources
But as far as I am concerned, this is not a very good answer, because it is not clear why people think resources are valuable
Economists just assume that resources are valuable to you
But in fact, what people think of as valuable is different
Not completely fixed, maybe you tend to think that food is of high value when you are hungry
But a lot of things we think have great value are a bit arbitrary, just like making a data
I am very interested in why people give value to something and what makes something valuable
Why believe certain things
How to make certain people believe in certain things,
Even risking his life to protect it
At least risking other people's lives
Maybe in the bigger picture, people finally have their own system
Belief system is not just a belief system, I started to understand it is not very appropriate
Too psychological
People will defend their belief system, this understanding is not completely correct
We have a shared belief system
Today’s phenomenon is due to its full sharing
We don’t know each other, we are a group of primates
We are in the same room and very peaceful, no one is frightened
It’s amazing, it shows that we all play our role
There are certain expectations for these roles
Matching the two is very important
We will discuss this in detail
This is not a belief system,
Even if it can match the actions of other people in the belief system
What you need to maintain is this match
You need to live your faith in the world
You want what you want to come true
It’s a good thing, you get what you want, you confirm your belief system, it’s good
But more often, we interact with each other, such as now
A series of expectations to pay and regulate our current behavior
For example, you don’t want me to take your tablet and break it,
This is shocking, you don't know what to do
Your situation will be different
You don't know where you are
This is another thing
Because there is a fundamental difference between being in a known and unknown environment,
You can think of this difference as the difference between the known and the unknown
If you bring a cat to a new house, the cat hates the new environment
Because in and around the old house, they have already inspected the surroundings
Check everywhere along the edge
Scared at first
They check everywhere, where they can hide, where they are safe
Because they went to these places and nothing happened
Think these places are safe
They slowly establish a comfortable neighborhood relationship
My dad used to take the dog for a walk. The cat was a little bored, so he followed him
Start along the house, around the building
Hide, then make hunting moves
After a while, the cat felt relieved and followed behind the dog
But he still has boundaries
If my dad took the dog from one block to more blocks,
The cat is sitting on the corner and crying
It’s like saying that I don’t want to go further, where I don’t understand
The difference between the areas that can be controlled and the areas that cannot be controlled is a fundamental difference
It's like the difference between home and strange unknown territory
Regarding the fields that people are familiar with, no one is more familiar than others
Because humans are social
Don’t understand territories too abstractly. Territory does not only refer to geographical and objective territory.
There are also levels within the territory
And the hierarchical structure has a predictable structure
Most of the time you know where you are best
So when you practice in it,
Usually get what you want
You are also excited about it
No one wants to be unstable around
Like you are walking somewhere
The people around should be very organized, but
We reorganize everyone and give them freedom
As a result, pain and dysfunction will appear. This is the consequence of absolute freedom.
When you pass by someone, he is muttering
Maybe something has been hit
When you make eye contact
Even in a situation like crossing the road, it will definitely make the other person notice
Then you want to keep your distance and
Hope it didn't attract the other party's attention
Because he is not in your rank
You can't predict what he might do
This is also an unexplored territory
Another way to think about this problem is
We are in time and space, and it is neither pure space nor pure time.
We are here and now
It's safe
Part of the sense of security comes from the physical structure,
Also because none of you behaves strangely
If someone behaves strangely
Such as standing up and yelling
Or attack the person next to him
The rest will be petrified in an instant
Because I suddenly entered an unknown territory
What you want is a calm lesson and learn some knowledge
The match between what you expected and what actually happened suddenly disappeared
Then you don’t know where you are
Don't know how to act
If you are a computer, the current state is down
but
You realize you are dying, it doesn’t help
First you will freeze
Then maybe consciousness is restored, or not, eyes wandering around
Sit there hoping no one notices you
This is the reaction to being hunted, just like the rabbit thinks the fox is staring at him
Humans are prey for a long time
Recently discovered
Lower teeth and mouth of prehistoric cat
be found
It matches the human skull very well, so the cat can bite through the human skull with this lower tooth
This is how the lower teeth evolved
Under such circumstances we have evolved into predators
But we are delicious hunters, and other hunters are happy to eat us
So when we don’t know how to respond, we will behave like a predator
Maybe this should be done when you bow your head and don't speak
They won't notice you
Maybe you will survive
On the contrary, maybe you decide to take the initiative
Knock down
but
Maybe you will become the exception instead of the norm, which is not surprising
We begin to understand how the belief system manages emotions
But not all spiritual
This is a bit like territorial management theory, not that there is a theory in your brain
But that the theory explains the world
So make you safer
It’s more like you have the theory in your mind
It makes you feel safe because it can explain the world
As for why this can explain the world because other people have also formed corresponding theories
When you all practice the theory
You all got what you wanted, this is a synergy of theory
The result will form your (personality)
life
Prevents you from falling into anxiety and often makes you happy because you get what you want
This is not just a psychological theory, but a practice in our lives, we cooperate with other sociologists
We match the belief system and act accordingly
Form an exact and productive society
In fact, fear management theory (proposed by Jeff Greengerg et al.) not only protects you from death anxiety
At the same time saved your life
This is good, (you) are protected from death anxiety,
This is good, but not very good, the fundamental thing you are after is
People have reasons to protect their territories
If you regard every citizen’s behavior as a fundamentally hypothetical field
Then there is a reason to defend it
If it falls apart, there will be a series of deadly chain reactions
This is chaos, chaos cannot bring people a stable mental state,
Chaos makes everything unstable, such as currency
Industry, economy, and electricity will also stop supplying
This is not a good thing
No wonder people have to defend it
Then I started to study what the belief system is
I realized that the belief system is actually a series of moral codes
Guide you how you should act
How to recognize
Know why ethical codes are necessary for you
It’s because you can’t know anything out of the hierarchy
Think about it, how many things you can see in this room
You can see countless things
There are squares everywhere, such as small squares on the screen
You can take a closer look until the end of time, but you didn’t do it
In fact, if I ask most of you,
Very few people can tell me the color of the wall
Even something on the wall
The reason is that no one cares
Wall won't move
I don’t want to care about the color, you have no reason to remember these
There is no emotional mark
No value
So what you would do is
This is what you are doing now, why are you here
Not a metaphysical philosophical question, but the specific reason why you are here
Obviously you are students
Want to get a degree
And believe that the degree has practical uses
Maybe you are a little smarter
Be good at thinking and writing better, which will make you more useful in the world
This is a good thing
Maybe you are interested, anyway
Now you are listening to this course
To get the corresponding degree
Then you can take care of your own life and meet someone who can build a long-term relationship
Get married and have children, and share corresponding roles in society
This is why you are here, all these reasons work together
This helps you decide what to focus on
So you are watching or listening to my lecture
Because in principle
At this moment I am a door leading to this series of life settings
So your attention is on me
This is why you think this is valuable
This means that without a value structure, you have no way of looking at the world
That is chaos, if everything is equally important or equally unimportant
This is confusion, so the value prompt,
To provide you with a way to recognize the world, this is not an abstract concept
There are enough experimental instructions
For example, the invisible gorilla experiment, how many of you guide this experiment, how many have not seen it
Roughly speaking, there are two teams
The white team and the black team wear clothes of corresponding colors
The video shows the players of the black team and the white team passing each other non-stop
Ask you in advance to count how many times the basketball has been passed by the black team members
Only one basketball
For whatever reason you work hard
You do what the experimenter asks you to do
Count the number of passes
It’s actually not that difficult, probably 16 times
You tell them it is 16 this, they say
Did you see the chimpanzee just now
Half of the laboratory subjects said, what are you talking about?
The experimenter said, let’s watch the video again, this time without counting the balls
About 30s in the video
The players fill the screen and they are not far away, like a group of ants playing basketball
You can see their faces clearly
About 1 minute, there is a person wearing a chimpanzee costume, he and the chimpanzee costume are all normal human size
He walked into the screen and punched his chest in the middle of the screen for about 5 seconds, then disappeared from the screen
More than half of the people did not notice this detail. Worse still, Dan Simon did another laboratory
You make a checkout counter in a store, there is a teller
You talk to the teller, then the teller squatted down
Like looking for something, and then another teller stands up
You think you will definitely notice this
But not actually
Even the differences between the staff are more obvious
People will not notice
When our attention is focused on a particular thing, we will not notice the others, because the others are not important
What we are doing
The teller is replaceable
As long as they play the role of teller
that's enough
and so
Belief system makes your cognition and value system structure, which can also be called value system
Structure your perception
And guide your actions because
Your actions are consistent with your value system
Whether it is conscious or unconscious, the value system is working, you don’t know just because you don’t know yourself
It can also be said that you have a value system that you don’t know
Sometimes you know this is a mistake, but you still get attracted to some people
Or you tell yourself to learn, but you don’t
You can’t control yourself with the goal of getting a degree
The more unified you are, the more you can control yourself, but you are more like a series of loose
Sub-personality that can argue with each other, more or less pointing to the same goal
But it depends on how much you want to achieve this goal, how carefully you think about it, and how possible it is
How many contradictions in your life have you ever eliminated,
In any case, the value system governs
Your thoughts and actions, we will be in the course
Learn a way of cognition, a very typical way of cognition
The typical meaning is
We will based on our expectation that our experience is true
In this way, the subject cannot be distinguished from the subject. This is not the way to be expected to work.
It’s more like you are doing a laboratory, including pain
Pain is not objective, but
The pain is real, one thing I understand is
You don't have to believe what I said
If you want to debate this
Why some parts don't make sense
From the thinking triggered by the person (on the street), what I want to express is, aside from basic assumptions, the conclusion I came up with
The conclusion has not been carefully confirmed, which does not mean
You can't try, you should try
Moral system
Tell you how to show what you see
The shared moral system keeps your emotions under control and satisfies your motivational needs
There is a David Hume
Old ideas
David. Hume
Very famous
He assumes that one thing cannot be assumed to be causally related to another
In other words, human beings only guide a few objective facts
Does not guide its application in life
There is a gap in between, maybe you would say
This is necessary for scientific work
One of the jobs of scientists is to strip the value of the object,
Because I don’t care about the particularity of the object to the individual
I want to understand how you perceive the object
It’s possible that everyone at least knows that
This can completely remove subjectivity,
This may just be a consequence of the scientific method
No moral orientation
People debate this, such as Sam Harris, scientific ethics are born
I don’t believe it, because I don’t think you can judge the value fairly, it’s too complicated
Value emerges by itself
Marxism puts forward the scientific utopia assertion, but it does not work in practice
In short
I agree with Hume in general
You can't say that one thing makes another thing
This is a problem
The first problem is that you have a set of facts, but you don’t know how to apply it.
For example, you should allocate money for AIDS or cancer or higher education
How to rationally calculate the pros and cons
There is no corresponding information as evidence
This is impossible
I used to work on the UN committee, the committee
You have hundreds of proposals on how to improve the world, but they are not sorted
You have to start with something, which means you have to pick an important proposal (you think)
Obviously in your life
If everything is equally important, you will be at a loss
Well known
A very simple example is
At the dawn of the scientific revolution
A wedge
Has been inserted into the heart of science, this is the moral system that unites us
The system may be a racial system
Has been severely criticized by science
This is very efficient, very useful criticism
Even if you hold traditional beliefs
The scientific onslaught is no joke
This is a problem that exists so far
You still don't know how to act
The philosopher Nietzsche would say
In the West, we run on top of Christian anger
Christianity has ruled for more than a thousand years, 1500 years, to be precise
It has developed a whole set of moral system based on a series of physical hypotheses
And form a social organization
These social organizations are based on specific beliefs, such as
What I say next may sanctify everyone’s ideas
Certain assumptions are put into the law, and certain deep-seated
E.g. natural human rights
This is an idea that is regarded as valuable by individuals and the law
Even if you have committed a crime or should be condemned
It’s a miracle why people think so
Roughly speaking
Humans tend to blame others
Suppose someone is accused of doing bad things
Was stoned to death or did anything else to him
Assuming innocence before there is evidence of a crime, my goodness,
Everything does not happen automatically, this concept is among the best
I dare not imagine how this happened, which gave me Xing Que
Because for me
There are some valuable ideas (things) beyond any individual assumption
I will not ask him to make scientific assumptions
Because this concept is more basic and fundamental
It is not unreasonable to make laws that society assigns personal value
Voting is subject to individuals
The fact is indeed the case, which gives the people the supreme power,
Such a society seems to work
But it is not certain that it will still work in the next 300 years
It has worked at least for the past 500 years
It's working well now, I assume most of you
Happy that the law empowers individuals
You have the right
Natural human rights
Show your superman value step by step
This insight rooted in Nietzsche
This is also rooted in a series of metaphysical concepts
His point is
If these metaphysical ideas are destroyed
Destroyed all the foundation stones
It may still take a long time for the entire Faith Building to collapse
It’s hard to say whether he’s right
In my opinion, what happened when Nietzsche foretold the death of God
19 actual late stage,
Western society oscillates between extreme trends
Such as Germany where the extreme left and extreme right coexist
Such as a democratic regime in a sense
Occupies the middle
There is no underlying metaphysical support, in my opinion
The regime is unsustainable
This is a problem because
No matter how you look at the underlying metaphysical ideas
The scientific method is true is not correct in itself
Because there is more than one kind of truth
I think there is a pragmatic truth
The truth is deeper than the truth of science
The truth of pragmatism makes your practice best,
Increase the possibility, roughly speaking, maximize your existence and replication
This is Darwin’s view, one of Darwin’s views
In my opinion, it is opposed to scientific materialism
Darwinism believes that there is no privilege to master knowledge
For example, people will die
If you know the world well, you will not die, in fact you will die
The knowledge you master can only make you live to 80
Maybe you will have children and they will survive
This is what evolution has done for 30 years
This is a pretty good solution
The program has good practicality, do we have better other practices
Our worldview is actually based on Darwinism
This may contain the truth of pragmatism
Instead of objective reality, pragmatic reality can be exploited
Make us alive, we care if we can live
We tend to use theory as a tool
It is possible
Tools can help us live
Recently I was reading Camille Paglia, one day
what
I found the similarities between us,
She is notoriously difficult person, I mean feminist
A classic modern feminist, even though she considers herself a feminist
Very smart, if you want to see how good someone’s eloquence is,
She is an expert in expression
You should read her book (video), in my opinion she is a bit fanatical,
She speaks quickly and coherently
Tore her opponent to pieces in the debate, she is very smart
One interesting thing she said is that she was influenced by some people, who happened to have influenced me.
She likes the origin and history of Eric Neumann’s consciousness
If you are interested in Jungian theory, I recommend this book
The book is a good introduction to the Jung school and the development of consciousness
And this book is based on the work of Jung and Joseph Cambell
And Mircea Eliade's, these are all criticized or ignored by postmodernism
Postmodernism believes that all humans have a central narrative
The center narrative
Is a necessary dramatic expression of the human value system
Rooted in our hearts
Form part of our nature, we have our nature as humans
We are not entirely shaped by culture
This is what postmodernism claims, the idea is dangerous
The danger lies in thinking that we are natural
Palia holds this view
The reason you came to university, you studied the humanities, or other possible reasons
It’s not about participating prematurely and criticizing and destroying something under the ignorant Qin Guang,
but
Study as much art, literature and poetry as possible
drama
Fiction
Rigorous thinking
All of these you can think of as
what?
This is the category of art, culture, music
We talk about music as if everyone loves it, or almost everyone
This is a mystery
You listen to music, it's interesting
Music will make people survive quite dark times. Why?
The answer is not obvious,
Music plays an important role on specific occasions in many cultures
I think you may find the most beloved music in your time
I heard it between your 16-20 years old
Like your mark
May define a whole generation
Maybe in the past tribal period, it was more like
The tribal customs that you were taught,
Dancing to the music with a mask
At the same time, you are invited to such occasions
And play a certain role in it
It is not correct to regard this as a representation of the objective world of things.
This is an invitation to enter the drama
Now the question may be transformed into, is the drama real?
the answer is
It depends on the true definition
I think great dramas are more real than real, they are super real
Because it abstracts it out and provides general guidelines
Used in a very wide range of situations
Let's imagine
You get up in the morning
Did a lot of things
Someone asks you what you are doing, what are you doing
You tell them to open their eyes first
Then I wonder if I should continue to sleep
Then lift the blanket and step on the floor
Stand up, blink and breathe while doing this
Then start looking for clothes. Do you really want to hear such an answer?
You don't want to listen, why are you telling me this?
I want to hear something interesting
What is interesting? And why are these things not interesting?
The answer is not obvious
Imagine this person tells you a very good story, a bit adventurous
Maybe
He is doing something very normal and something unusual has happened
He had to find a way to respond
Has he solved this problem? This is what interests you
Especially when he gets it done, because
When he tells you how he handles certain unexplored areas
He will also systematize it
Maybe when you encounter such a situation, you can handle it accordingly
This is quite cheap wisdom for you, he has to find a solution
All you have to do is listen
This is a classic story, roughly speaking
This kind of story is usually about a man or a woman, it doesn’t matter
Life is quite normal
Suddenly hit, they fell into chaos
Chaos is such a place
Stop what you are doing
The world no longer matches (with your cognition), chaos can be divided into many degrees, such as when you wake up
Found that your room was stolen, and your parents had Alzheimer’s disease,
Or some serious diseases
Or your family is murdered, the war begins,
There are many levels of confusion
You can
Judge the degree by calculating how much you were interrupted by the event
The higher the interruption, the higher the instability
This is why if someone tells you that you will be destroyed in pain within 3 months,
Is very bad
You are facing an unpredictable field, your original assumptions and ideas are not true
Generally speaking, the world is no longer real
We like to see people lead their usual lives
Blind to some things
Going through the transition period when it just entered a state of chaos,
Collect new information
Reshape their personality, or reshape the world, both are solutions
Then come out from the other side
Things are better than they were at the beginning
At least not bad, good results, right?
This is a good ending, comedy, technically
You want your life to be a comedy
But not funny
Because comedy doesn’t have to be funny,
Just the opposite of tragedy
The tragedy is that when you go through these things, you choose to blindly see, (seems) to handle it well
This situation does happen, at any time. But what you want is comedy
right now
I hope I can provide you with a magic code
A book was released a while ago
Movie starring Tom Hanks
He was a professor at Harvard University, solving symbol-related puzzles
Do you remember what this is called
Da Vinci Code, everyone loves it, this book is a big hit
It’s full of small mysteries and all kinds of hints. These hints about the world are beyond your imagination.
This is absolutely true
There are ways to learn this knowledge, and it's worth it
People like this idea because of its authenticity
Just like the novel is true, let’s go back to telling you what happened after you got up in the morning.
If he tells something exciting,
Imagine 10 people tell you something exciting
You will extract a picture of such things
Then when you are a writer, you will apply it to the book
In the book, you don’t want the plot to be about ordinary people
Doing normal things in their lives
You already know how to be an ordinary person, but it doesn’t help writing novels
After all, no one wants to watch a video about himself
Imagine you record your own day and watch it the next day
You will think, oh my god, who would want to watch this
So in the story they will refine
They observe people,
They told the story they saw, but removed most of the story
All the boring content is removed, hope so
Exciting story details stack up
Maybe a great writer was born and write some really interesting stories
Significant role transformation
And when you say it's fiction
You would say it's not true
Because he is fictitious
But this is not necessarily correct
Maybe more real
Because who wants truth, truth is ordinary reality, you have already mastered it
What you want is refined
Interesting experience
Maybe you will say, why is it interesting, this is a good question, because you are not really
Understand and believe me, you don’t know why you find meaningless things interesting
Today I will start with Pinocchio, I will talk more about it next time
I want to talk a little bit about how this movie started, and you will know how crazy you are
You all know the plot, how many of you have seen Pinocchio?
Many people
Many people have seen
This thing itself is quite strange
It’s worth thinking about, usually you tend to show such movies to children
But if you think about the movie content
I think it’s weird to sit down and watch this movie
First of all, this is a sketch animation with very low resolution
You don’t care, you may also watch the Simpsons
There is also a cartoon dedicated to mocking politics: South Park
The animation of this cartoon really sucks out of the sky
Yes, it sucks, it can't be worse
You don't care
Round head,
Smiles and eyes like fans, you can only tell that this is a person
It’s all irrelevant, even if you use higher pixels, it won’t help.
You only need a summary,
To feel attached
therefore
You watch these animations, Pinocchio, very beautiful animations
play in order
You are not watching something real, you are watching purely broken structures
Recall the plot
Very ridiculous, everything is ridiculous
One character is insect
It feels like consciousness, what the hell is this?
Another character is a puppet, a marionette
For some reason he escaped from the rope and started an adventure
Then he was lured by a fox and a cat
To different evil places
Then he rescued his father from the whale
You don’t even know how his father got into the belly of a whale, the last time you saw his father
It was in heavy rain, and what happened next was that he was in the belly of a whale
You sit there and think, "Hey, no problem, that makes sense."
what? Really?
why?
Why does this make sense?
The answer is you don't know
This is cool
You don't know, you don't even know what you are looking at
But it doesn't matter
You watch it and you are interested, you want to know what happened to this doll
Do you want to know if he eventually became a real boy
Because this looks important
You ask: Is Pinocchio real?
This is a stupid question
Because the answer is that it depends on how you define reality
and
The definition is not obvious to me
When you say something is true
What should you express
The answer is not obvious because
There is such a concept in our society and its influence is far-reaching. This concept is that the ultimate reality is the scientific reality.
This tells us the world itself, in some ways
Indeed, there is no objection
Physicists have discovered the correct law, which is why we can make hydrogen bombs. This is a strong evidence of scientific correctness.
But even if it’s true you don’t know how to practice
You observe things, are attracted and confused by them
No inference can be formed based on the known construction
to me
What the world is made of is a question, another bigger question is
How do you interpret yourself in the world
This is what you really want to know, more than any other question
Because you need to know, like you are in college now, but don’t know what you are doing
Some people know a little bit more than others
But you are still in the early days of life,
Life is very complicated and chaotic
It’s not obvious what kind of relationship you should build
What kind of personality should you shape
What kind of job do you want to do
Or what is the meaning of life, this is a good question, what is the meaning of life
As you know, people come to college, at least most, want to figure out the answer to this question
Now paglia, her opinion is
You should think like this, clear knowledge
Contained in unclear knowledge
The unclear knowledge is
Literary and artistic
High-level culture
We probably know what this means
But we can’t clearly know its meaning, its meaning is more than we know
The outside is the realm we all know
This is the point of view of Jungian theory, and perhaps Paglia got it from it
Because Jung believed
In any field, there are parts that we fully control
Beyond this you see it as an unexplored field
When our creative imagination meets the unknown,
We will use creative imagination
To figure out how to deal with the unknown, we created drama
And perform plays, which can help us deal with things that we can’t control
We know nothing outside of this field
Paglia’s view is also Jung’s view,
Don’t understand what’s around you will be too
Atomization
You are not part of your historical tradition
You haven't absorbed the spirit of your ancestors
Ancestors established all these traditions
You just exist in the present
You don’t know what to do, you don’t know how to maintain your tradition, and you don’t know how to serve it
You may ask why you should serve the traditional
I have an imaginary,
You can think of it this way, I don’t know if this is correct, but
The meaning of people’s lives, for me
The meaning is to take appropriate responsibility
You know, for example
You have a three year old sister
You have to take care of her
It seems silly to question whether this is a good idea
I mean, this is not a question to ask
obviously
Self-explanatory, this is what you have to do
Do you want to find meaning in it?
You are interacting with a child
When I have children, they are 2 years old or younger
We take them out for a relative
They are older
They looked at a 2-year-old child like a fire
Every second the child is in the house
Every adult
Are following them
This is what people tend to do
This is a certain meaning, what else is meaningful, your family members are meaningful to you
Maybe the sense of responsibility as a friend is also meaningful
Maybe you decide to pursue a career and become a useful person in society
Some of the dominant factors are
Because of your desire to be safe or to succeed, that makes sense
But you also
Need to play a complete role in the social structure, which supports you, my observation is
In my consultation process, when people have nothing to do
There is too much time to run out,
I have to go to work at 9:00 in the morning, the arrangements are very strict
Maybe I should be grateful for this, I noticed that when people break away from external system constraints
They are like floating
They will be depressed and restless, they don’t know what to do, just like sled dogs are not pulling a sled
We are like sled dogs, carrying weights, we need to carry weights
The question is what kind of load do we need
The reason we need is
I have thought about what the truth is for a long time,
Because i am an existentialist
My actions are based on the premise that you can infer what people believe by observing how people behave
I don't care what they say
I don’t care what they claim to be their opinion of truth
Because speaking and doing are directly related
Sometimes very low or even non-existent
One thing I noticed is
No one will argue with others about their pain
Everyone injured
Behave like they believe the pain is real
So we can say
The ultimate truth is pain
This is what people show
The claims in this multi-ethnic tradition are consistent
Jesus always
Recall the pain of the past
I mean that the God of Christianity was crucified. This is painful. For Buddhists, the most basic belief is that living is suffering.
In my opinion this is a philosophical view
This view holds that the pain is real
Of course it really depends on your definition of truth
But people always act as if the pain is real, this is a starting point for thinking about problems
Now this points to a problem
Life is painful
Life is miserable, why
Because you will get hurt
And destroyed
It seems self-explanatory, you know
It also makes people unique. This is our consciousness, right?
In a sense, this can really distinguish humans from other creatures.
I mean, some other creatures are also self-aware, like chimpanzees
You can learn to recognize yourself in a mirror, and so can dolphins
But this is a very conceptual sense of self
True self-awareness is to recognize one's own boundaries
Not only space, but also time
So far, humans are the only creatures that can discover the future
This is great because we can plan for the future, but it also has disadvantages
Because the future is limited, this is a big shock to the old system
Everyone bears and endures pain is a burden of reality
Then you think, life is suffering and finite, this is also part of suffering
This will prompt you to question the value of existence
Existence itself may be value
One of the weapons against the emptiness of existence
It’s the sense of responsibility we mentioned earlier, it feels feasible
How much responsibility do you take in your relationship with things
It looks like
It can improve your sense of meaning when you participate, maybe you will say, when is meaningful participation,
How about alleviating a little bit of suffering
You know, in your life this can be
Reduce unbearable pain, especially meaningless pain
This is a good thing, maybe you can be more useful,
You can solve some of your suffering and other people’s sufferings like hitting a home run,
Maybe you will find a way to heal you
If pain makes you question life, it makes sense
This end of pain
Minimize suffering
As a result of logical inference, it should be a suitable compromise
I would say it means
There are some patterns
Can make you immerse yourself in it and become a better person
and
One of the benefits of being a good person is
Can alleviate suffering
You should have no doubts here
If suffering itself makes you question the value of life
Then you can’t say it’s useless when the pain can end
You can say this, but it is actually inconsistent. If you want, you can declare the inconsistency.
I think
These refined stories
From a great author
I especially admire Dustoevsky
his job
He is the best novel among the authors I have read so far
No one can surpass, he can deal with the most difficult problems of mankind
He can simultaneously shape the argument of opposite roles, and indeed makes the debate fully revealed
This is not to say that Dostoyevsky
There is a concept, and then the concept of giving him the role, which makes this role always win the debate
This never happened in Dostoyevsky’s novels
You set the character, then set 3-4 opponents
These opponents are not scarecrows, they are like steel giants
They trample on the protagonist ruthlessly, this is a war of different ideas between the protagonist and the opponent
It's amazing to read
Great writers can distill stories
The great storyteller refines the story
Some stories are very very old
It is often religious stories in various forms, and some can also be myths
Because mythology can be traced back 10,000 years ago
This is part of oral tradition
Oral tradition can exist for thousands of years
If a story has been told for ten thousand years, it must be a very interesting story and people must remember it
Obviously it has also been modified. It's like a game of spreading. Let me tell you one thing. Tell you one with a laugh. Keep going.
Lasted for thousands of generations
The last part that people remember is the part they think is important, because people tend to remember what they think is important
What this means is not necessary for you, you don’t know the meaning of music
but
This is not preventing you from listening to music
You usually don’t know what a movie or book you’ve seen is talking about
Because they have multiple meanings, they are usually deeper than you can understand
Otherwise why read it
There is a view like this
You need to be rooted in the moral system, which is described by words
Can be drama
The moral system can guide us in life
The reason for understanding this is that at some level you can understand
Because you need to know how to survive
Nietzsche said if you have a problem and you can bear it
This is good, the guards of Auschwitz once did one thing to prisoners
It’s worth mentioning that there is a slogan in Auschwitz
Work makes you free
This is actually a joke
Not very funny
This is a joke that has to be evil
Conceptualize in a suitable time
Then be declared
When Osconsin’s range arrived, they were already in very bad condition
They were sent in a truck
They are classified with their families and deprived of everything
Tossing around for a long time and standing still
Because there is not enough space, the children have difficulty breathing and the space is very small
No food, no toilet
There is about 20% of the death rate during transportation, and people standing outside the livestock cart were frozen to death
Very cruel
When they arrive in Wisconsin, the guards will play this game
They will say that work makes you free
They will find a prisoner,
This prisoner is dying
Let them carry a sack of damp salt, about 100 pounds
From one end to the other
You might think that the prison is the size of a football field with protective nets around it, but it’s not
This is like a city, there are thousands of people
It’s a long walk from one end to the other.
This is not bad enough, they have to move the bag of salt to the starting point
To this malicious poetic statement is what is being done
Is to use human force for useful activities
It's okay to skim away the difficulties
Looks like this is a bad thing
People need
Meaningless parody,
People need meaning because life is hard
Problem makes
What is your purpose in life
Another question may be, does it matter whether the word is interesting
Because what matters is what matters, but what matters is what matters
I think what matters is more real than what matters
At least you behaved like this, then the question is, should you set a goal?
This is a good question, this question is about the meaning of life
One thing that should happen when you come to university
Yes basically find the answer to this kind of question
so far
Maybe I’m too cynical, the college students I saw,
Attached to the remains of their culture
Floating around like fragments
These fragments will be taken away by the professors who told them that anything can be broken,
No, these ideas have no practical meaning
When you finally graduated, it was like duckweed flowing to the ocean, you left nothing
You're done, you can graduate
But i don't see anything useful in it
In contrast to
I tell you a story
First of all, I’m going to give you suggestions, which we will elaborate on
You live in a story, through the frame of the story
Looking at the world, it’s like a story,
When this story is where you are
And you are going to somewhere else
This can be conceptualized,
There is a gradient between where you want to go and your goal,
What are you doing when you sit there
Assuming your goal is better things
Usually you are in an insufficient state
Insufficiency changes
Then you try to correct the deficiency
It is generally believed that your current state is always not as good as the state you want to achieve
Usually the way you bridge the gap is
Sometimes you can think
But the more essential situation is through practice
You through practice in the world
This can partially answer the mind-body question
You have a conceptual structure and when you apply it
It is not abstract, you use it through practice
This is the most basic story, not so attractive
But this is a framework for you to see the world, a framework that carries value
Otherwise you can’t practice and you can’t understand how to look at (the world)
This is a value-laden framework
Through this framework, we can say what is the starting point of the best value framework
This is the problem we are trying to figure out
Now I’m going to talk about the war between the communists and the western world.
Why does it attract me
One thing is
I really want to know about autocracy
Similar to communists and the West, there are certain axioms
If you are a moral relativist, you might say
A certain type of axiom set is better
Even, think that a series of axioms, one system is better than another
This is the point of view of a moral relativist, and you know
So before I thought it might be more arbitrary by force
This is how people deal with two competing systems (arbitrary statement)
No room for discussion and negotiation
I have been thinking about this for a long time, I want to know
Where are the roots of the Marxist system and the Western system
I guess the western system is formed after long-term evolution
And the communist system is imposed by rationalists
It's not the same thing, then i want to know
Where is Western culture rooted, and is there any reason why it is reasonable on any level?
This prompted me to study and learn the underlying story
Based on the basic stories of our culture, I believe that some of them are very old
Next, I will tell the story of Mesopotamia, which is one of the oldest stories we know, and the story of Egypt.
These are the origins of our culture
I think these stories are rooted in older traditions
They map some reality
Very real,
I mentioned before
There are different ways and concepts to understand the truth
My initial hypothesis is that you might also think it is an axiom
Pain is the most real, because this is how people behave.
You can criticize it
Of course you can also come up with other alternative conceptual frameworks, such as those used by scientists
Because they believe it is important to pursue the truth of things
Maybe we need more than one way to interpret the world
this is possible
Now what I want to say is what I think is the most essential
Elements that make up the story
I hope one of them is
Knowing it can make you
Immune to ideology
The reason is that I think ideology is intermittent and incomplete
Meta-narrative, the reason they have power is
They are rooted in meta-narratives, but they only tell part of the story
But they still have power because they are rooted in the essential narrative
Its characteristic is
People tend to characterize the world, we are social primates
We tend to see the world through the glasses of social roles
Because we practice in the world and the world is full of other people
So we conceptualized it into personality terms based on this structure,
To guide action
The most essential reality is chaos
You can't understand confusion
Settings cannot be conceptualized
You can only touch the edge of chaos
When the twin towers collapsed
The chaos occupied quite a while and everyone was in shock
This is chaos, it is your experience when your story falls apart
Fall under the unknown
This is chaos, basically you live in order and chaos, order is
You know what to do when and where, and you get what you want
Also known areas to be explored
Chaos is when you do something and hope for a certain result,
But it didn't happen
At this point you will be in chaos
Chaos has different depths,
When chaos occurs, your life can fall apart very badly
, Like falling to hell
You are in chaos and realize that it is your own problem
You did something wrong
You know and ignored it
This is your bad mess
When chaos occurs
What followed is very straightforward
You can think of individuals in culture
Culture is contained in nature
Naturally matrilineal
Culture is patrilineal
I think this is because of the hierarchical structure of human nature
Is machismo
Nature is likened to a woman because
Two reasons, one is that all women play the role of sexual selection in human history
From the perspective of Darwinism
Second, because it is naturally biologically productive
We often conceptualize men and women
To organize the world
This is a metaphor
But far beyond metaphor, it is reasonable to compare culture to a picky father
because
Because a group of people gather around you, some are friends, some see how you work, some evaluate you
After a long time of evolution
These people accumulate to form an entity
Constantly review and criticize you
It is also reasonable to personify it
It’s like a Yuanren is watching you
This is a useful analogy, there is a meta-man who is watching you
Yes it is obvious
You can say it's not real
It’s not true on the scientific level, but it’s also another form of truth.
Nature has two elements, destruction and creation
Nature has a beautiful and generous side
It’s also Anopheles, Elephantiasis, Cancer
The terrible side of hunger
And culture is authoritarian
Because you have to shape yourself (to adapt to the culture), unconsciously get along with other people,
You have to sacrifice many parts of yourself and develop yourself
As a result, we have to balance ourselves to adapt to social life
Some societies are more authoritarian than others
But they all have authoritarian elements, and it’s no exception on college campuses, you all know
Big here
It’s easy to feel like you’re overwhelmed like numbers, it doesn’t matter whether you are here or not
The school doesn’t care, it’s authoritarian
But the school cares because you are here and you are receiving education
Maybe this is the positive side
Each feature has two sides
Nature has positive and negative properties
Culture also has a positive and negative nature, including individual
The individual is like standing on an island in the center of the ocean
The place you are in has a positive concept
Solid ground, limited extension, other parts you don’t know
As an individual you also have positive and negative elements
There are heroes and villains
Of course, if there are no heroes and villains in the story, what else to see
The villain is the part that people show that should not be shown, the hero is the part that should be shown
When you watch a movie or read a book, there are heroes and villains in it
To some extent this will give you a concrete understanding of the villain
When you meet about 30 villains, you will have a conceptual understanding of what villain behavior is
This is the core element of the villain
No matter what
You can imagine building a meta villain for you
Or meta heroes, these are the characters in the old stories
in general
In the Marvel movie
There is Odin, he has two sons
Thor and Vulcan Loki,
Thor is a recognized hero, Vulcan is a liar who always wants to destroy everything
You can identify these by yourself
This is useful because even if you underestimate
[Student question] Is this a positive spirit?
No, this is a map of meaning
Positive spirit
Certainly not
Why might you become vicious?
First because you can
This is critical
This is actually a branch of empathy
It took me decades to figure out
What I want to understand when I study Genesis
In this book
When people become conscious, they immediately understand good and evil
I can't understand, what is the connection between these?
I think this problem is about 30 years
I want to solve this mystery, and then I want to understand
When you are self-aware
You can conceptualize yourself as a creature
You know what you are
You know what you look like
Know what can hurt you and what can't
Soon, you know what can hurt you
You know what can hurt her
Good and evil also arise with self-consciousness
There are some characteristics that make humans fundamentally different from other species
Lions eat you
But it won't torture you slowly
Just for pleasure
It just eats you
You can think this is evil, it must be very bad
But animals are actually beyond the concept of good and evil, but humans,
We can be very evil, we are very good at it
Because we will imagine that if it hurts me, it will hurt you too
You need to know your possible behavior, because this is you
If you think you wouldn't
Actually you will behave similarly more than you think
Because the people who have this behavior most often are those who think they will never do it
You need to fight it
This is why in many systems conceptualizing the world is a war between good and evil
This is a reasonable conceptualization
Meta concept
Culture is a wise and authoritarian king, always like this
You are often stuck in it, because as an individual, you have both positive and negative sides
The negative side is full of resentment and is easily provoked
Is limited
Suffering is inevitable, this is the tyranny and unfair side of nature
No wonder you have a dark side
This is not a trivial matter
In the Karamazov brothers, arguing is very artistic
There is a character called Alise, he is a monk apprentice, not outstanding in talent
But he is a good man. His brother is called Ivan, who is a genius for evil
One of the ways Ivan tortured Allese was to tell a story that Dostoevsky later changed into a new story
This story is about a pair of parents taking their little daughter
Once locked her out all night
It was very cold outside, she stayed outside crying and screaming until she died of freezing
Ivan will basically give Alese these
Something that shouldn't have happened in reality
This is a good argument, you can even cite thousands of similar examples
Part of us is always trying to prevent us from being, full of resentment
This is a good idea
As far as I know, if you show this
It will make you worse
Maybe you should be happy about it
You might think that people don’t do such things when they are conscious
But they will
I recommend you to read Karpenzram (Perverted Murderer), if you are interested in such issues
The author of this book raped thousands of men and killed dozens
Do your best to destroy everything
Want to start a war between Britain and America
No goal except killing
He wrote an autobiography at the request of a doctor who also encountered his
He recorded in detail what he did and why he did it
this story
Heroes and opponents
Order and power, destruction and reconstruction
This is the most basic picture outside of chaos, let’s rest for a while
This is another way of looking at
The individual may concentrate, explore, master
Or distracted elsewhere
People stay in the explored field
This is the unexplored field
No matter where you go, you have two opposing halves
You have to fight for yourself
No matter where it is, as long as there is a human society, there is autocracy and beneficial nature
In a sense, society is what you are doing matches what is happening
This is very important, unexplored area
No matter when and where, your experience is invalid
This is not a geographical concept, because when you think about a known field
What you think of is the geographical realm, like an animal land, your house
This must be an element of the territory, but you know
When you are at your home, a snake sneaks into your living room, you are right there
There is a major difference between the house 1 second ago and your house now
Your house can become unknown as soon as the hat drops because you are in time and space
Unexplored areas are conceptualized
This is a conceptual field, which refers to when your experience is not available wherever you are
Human experience has its permanence
This is what I think is the basic element in our narrative
This is part of you
There are some themes of stories
The subject is a self-contradictory person with many different potentials
You are always with other people somewhere
Because this is our territory
I mean social animals
Even our ancient ancestors, many of their territories
There are other primates too, we classify the world into accumulating characteristics
This is very important to us, and it is our tendency to look at the whole world
Uncharted territory
Is where you don't know how to act
But when you don’t know what to do, you actually know what to do
This is quite normal, our pressure feedback system will behave as
Freeze, generally speaking, if the threat is big enough
You secrete a lot of cortisol and adrenaline, which can make you
Always ready to act fast
If you pay attention
This is what you do when you don’t know how to do it, the problem is that you can stay in this state forever
This is also a traumatic post-stress disorder state
You will always be in this state
The problem is that it’s very uncomfortable
When you stay in this state for a while, you will feel frustrated
Will produce disorderly anxiety and you will grow old
Because it consumes a lot of energy and energy quickly
Your body system has been delaying all problems to respond to the current state of emergency
It's very energy consuming
This is not what you want
This is one of the reasons why people tend to defend their territories
because
If their familiar territory is invaded or disturbed
They will enter a state of emergency
This will strip you away and have a profound impact
You understand this state
When people are betrayed by someone in close relationships, they usually
Will experience this feeling
Or people lie
The dream I've been pursuing is broken
Or family members’ illness or death, etc., but betrayal is the most typical
Because you have been with someone for a long time and you trust him
In this relationship you represent your past and present
You describe this relationship
And the future related to it
You’ve been betrayed, it’s like bum, even the past is different from what you once thought
about you
You have no clue
Why is it so easy to be deceived, you don't know, is this your fault?
So stupid that I can't protect myself
Or others are so vicious that you don’t even notice
Everything is floating in the air, it's no good
There is also a concept that humans travel around the underground world
Come back again, this is a useful way to understand, because
We often do
Whenever we fail, it’s like suddenly falling into the underground world
Everything is in chaos there
Maybe we organize ourselves and come back again
So, a way to conceptualize yourself, not order
Not chaos
But in between
I think it’s a mythical hero
So I will start with Pinocchio
Quite weird
I hope you can find fun in it
Why start with Pinocchio because
Because I hope to introduce the abstract knowledge mentioned above into examples
So easy to think
To conceptualize knowledge like I said above, are they good for everything?
Do they help
This is the order in the chaos in hiding
Establishment of order
Heaven has fallen, secular history
Heaven is rebuilt, this is a classic comedy
Is also a story of life
The question is how much you can control him
Everyone wants to know the answer to this question
Very weird, you will pay
Pay online to see related stories
Even if you don’t know what these stories are really telling
The reason is
Some part of you knows what these stories are telling
Your perception is hierarchical
You understand things you don't know
Through many ways you don’t understand, you can feel
We mentioned a little Pinocchio story, which is ridiculous
But not important
Student - I have a question, is chaos that people do not act in a way that you expect and cause you negative emotions,
Something bad happened
What if the opponent’s actions are very positive, such as winning a big lottery
You still get into a stress response, or?
This is the same situation
No, this is not the same situation, this is a good question
Let's think about it
Usually winning the big lottery is not good for people
This amount is too much
To them
Has changed their lives drastically
The best situation is to continue living their previous emotions and life as much as possible
But this is indeed a great thing
I mean, at least better than other very bad things
But it still brings instability
It depends on what element in your life it will disrupt
It can be understood that you have a map of action in the world
This map is either superficial or profound
Different preset composition
When the profound preset is destroyed
Huge blocks in the map will be invalid
sometimes
It also occurs when particularly severe positive events occur
When the basic law, the more concepts are disturbed,
Harder to recover
When you win the big lottery, maybe you will quit your job
I want to go to the beach, I want to have a Margarita
Maybe you can be cool for a few days in this state
When you live a life of drunkenness and dreams for 3 months on the beach, it can be considered an improvement.
It’s not as easy as it seems, when you make people deviate from their daily routine
They will be confused
Their routine is broken, they don’t eat normally, and they don’t know what to do
This is why retirement is difficult for many people
I am about to retire
When I relax for two weeks, maybe I will die
I need to do something
I need to devote myself to something
Closer to home
Pinocchio, an early Disney movie, very genius
So I will lead you to interpret
And tell you what I think it means
You can also express your thoughts, which is beneficial to our understanding
Today I will only talk for 10 minutes, try to be as detailed as possible
We will continue next class
Beginning of the video
Cast list
Is carved on wood, which is a hint
Because Gaby is a carpenter, the background music is
A very popular song
a little bit
Uh, how would you describe it
I do not think so
This is a very profound poem
But this is a song that people love and listen to today
Set the tone of the movie, this is the role of music
One of the most mysterious things about the film is
When you watch a movie, there is always background music
If the movie has no background music
It feels a little hollow, like missing something
When you watch a movie, there are a lot of things you can’t see,
For example, the role is partial
You don’t understand the background, it’s like low resolution
The role of music seems to provide an emotional background to the complex context of the film
Like some kind of substitute for content
Guide you into the video settings
It gives a hint that the movie is about to happen
The most interesting thing is that we have no objections to this
Just like the movie has background music
When the plot changes drastically, the music also changes drastically
But it doesn’t happen in real life (background music)
Maybe you are wondering why we can accept music in the film
Part of the reason may be that we tend to accept exaggerated reality
This makes up the movie
In fact, we found that the ability of music to amplify dramatic effects is very significant
We can accept
This song is very interesting, so I plan to analyze it a little bit
Sometimes I feel stupid to do this, because this song is a bit childish
This is a childish song
But it’s okay, when you make a wish to the stars, it doesn’t make you any different
Yes, people wishing to the stars is a somewhat mysterious act
Some sense of ritual
why
People want to do
What exactly do the stars represent
This is another question
Because the stars shine in heaven
Some people are stars
Why do people make stars to chase stars
Stars are usually very famous people,
They attract a lot of attention
Maybe these people are very talented,
Maybe they are idols, not just supermodels, they are imitated
This is what it means to be a star, and why the magazine is full of stars
Like they are heroes brought to the world
Of course you don’t know anything about them, only the public image
Of course they are usually charming
People will project the perfect personality on them
They are stars
But why make stars to chase stars? Stars can be summoned in the dark, right
They are from another world
They don’t belong to the earth, this is a cool place
Technically
The stars obviously do not belong to the earth,
And in terms of phenomena, it is like an element of human experience
Many of you are from the city
There is not much experience and opportunity to see the night sky full of stars
This is a pity because
The starry night sky is awe-inspiring
Naturally you will feel this
When you look up, the stars are all over the night sky
You are looking at the edge of the Milky Way, the milky white band
You will be amazed
This is the edge of the Milky Way
There are countless stars, very vast, like looking towards infinity
Look into the unknown, look beyond you
Definitely
This makes people feel awe, like seeing a huge canyon or similar picture
You are looking at something beyond yourself, this sense of awe
Is a natural part of our feedback system
Maybe you will feel awe when you meet someone you respect and desire
Because you think they have something extraordinary
Have a very interesting idea
There are people you admire and don't admire
This is a clue to your value system
Maybe you can’t tell why you find some people attractive
Admirable
It’s like you’re looking for something that you can admire
Hypothesis
The person you admire has a certain ability
You also want to have
So they became idols to be imitated
This is part of the reason why people develop, just like some children often treat older children as heroes
Not much older than them, usually within their understanding
They will follow such children and imitate them
They imitate people they admire
The fact that you admire certain people or things provides clues to understanding your unrealized value system
Even as an exercise
What kind of human qualities I admire, you need to ask yourself
You haven’t really considered this, there is a clear difference between asking yourself questions and thinking about them
Because when you ask yourself a question, you think
What do I find about admiration?
You don't know the problem
If you are lucky, this will happen regularly, and the answers may often be wild
You can write it down
You have some ideas about what your ideals, you know, and maybe you already have a
Your ideal match is a star
When you make a wish to the starry sky, you look up at the starry sky
The spirit gathers on something beyond yourself
Focus on the starry sky shining in the dark night
Now the stars mean
People who wear jewelry, because jewelry is like stars
Or like the sun
Pure and perfect and shining,
So some matter about the source of light
This is the source of enlightenment and illumination
So the light shining in the night sky is a very deep metaphor
This is what you want, you want light to shine in the dark night
The stars have all these characteristics, so people make wishes for the stars
Because they have some intuition that can surpass the ordinary
Has the potential to reshape, they make a wish
When you want to make a wish
You should set high goals!
Even just like wishing a wish come true
This is not a metaphor
You know that I have a plan, you all will color jade
Called the future writing plan
This is one of two assignments, one of which is writing an autobiography
This is writing about the past, the other is writing about planning for the future
Called Future Writing, I suggest you start preparing immediately
Not right away, but start very quickly, because it’s harder than you think
Some of you will write about 15,000 words
You will find yourself writing poorly, this always happens
So you write an autobiography to find out where you are from
Who are you or how do you plan for the future unless you know where you are from
Then you have to write the future by hand because
When you don't have a goal, you don't have focus
Definitely
Most of the time people don’t focus on the goal because they are afraid
The reason for fear is that when you know what to do, you also know the conditions for failure
You know when you fail
It’s better to continue to feel fuzzy, like I don’t know if I succeeded or failed
This is difficult to describe in detail. well! Except when you don’t focus on the target you can’t get
So the future writing plan is like
Make you have to clearly try to describe yourself
So who are you in the past writing plan?
Past writing plans required breaking down your life into multiple periods
Write down things about emotions, that is, some important events
These events shape who you are
You will find that writing like this will make you emotional
If you have more than 18 months of memory, generally speaking
When you remember it again, there will be an emotional shock
Especially negative emotional shock
Just like part of your soul goes back and gets stuck there
This is a figurative way of thinking, I mean
Now you can still feel emotional because you still have not solved the problem in this situation
Face it, maybe this is the crux that some people still struggle with when you face it
These people are bad, it’s very difficult, because you have to deal with the problem of evil
Similar questions, this is no joke
If this still generates emotions, you have not solved the problem
Your brain still sees it as a threat, this is an area you have not mastered
Threat, threat, threat
Knowing you knock it down, expression is a useful way, writing is a useful way
The place where you are threatened will not let you free
It feels unpleasant, when you deal with these situations
In the short term will tend to produce emotional decline
But it was back to normal after about 3-6 months
Unfortunately, people often face this situation and must not do what they don’t want to do
This is very common
So the future writing plan asks you to thank you for the different dimensions of your life
Because you can see yourself as the personality in your head
You are embedded in a system that transcends you, as real as any thought that appears in your mind
What you need in your life
This is easy to answer, some friends
Intimacy, family, are good things
No matter what will happen or what you already have,
To some extent, from these things, people feel love and care for each other, which is also a good thing
You need a career plan, you need to find a position to make others value it and treat you equally
You can live
When you are not at work, you need to use the time to do something worthwhile
You also need to pay attention to your physical and mental health
Need to adjust and plan your asset use
This is one of the weird points, because a lot of people drink, so it’s worth thinking about, and that’s why we put it forward
The next question, what do you want?
What do you want from your friends
What to get from your family
What you get from your career
If you can get what you want, this is the question this plan asks you
After about 3-5 years of planned life, you can get what you want
I assume that your goals or expectations are like a sane adult
Instead of being like a 13-year-old dreamer, I want the most expensive yacht in the world
This is OK, but,
This does not focus on the original intention of the writing plan, allowing you to focus more on your character
Then you are asked to write for 15 minutes, almost without thinking, without considering issues such as grammar or sentence structure
About your life in the next 3-5 years
If you care about yourself
You will help (future self) imagine what he needs
Then the plan requires you to do the same thing in the opposite way
After rational consideration of various situations
Your shortcomings
I guess everyone knows
But everyone has the intuition to reduce their shortcomings
Some people are addicted to alcohol, some are on the streets
Certainly something fatal happened to produce this result
If you are particularly careless
Don't let things fall apart and fall apart
So hope you write it down
About what you don’t want to happen in the next 3-5 years
This has a psychological basis
If you have goals, this is the source of positive emotions
Because there is evidence that positive emotions usually come from when you are close to something that makes you valuable
Only completing certain plans cannot generate excessive positive emotions
Because when you finish something, you leave the problem that you will face next time
When you graduate from university
Yay!
You cannot graduate from university one day,
Then you will be unemployed, looking for a bad job like Starbucks
You understand what i mean
The problems you need to solve one after another
If you keep thinking that you will be happy when all the problems are solved
Hahaha! good luck
but
When you work towards something worthwhile, you believe it is worth it
You thought about it, you know, so you won’t be weak, because you cheer yourself up
Then when some progress is made, even if only a little bit, you think, hey, not bad,
You will release a small dose of dopamine
This makes what you want, this is the source of your positive emotions
Cocaine can also achieve this effect, but
This is bad for you in the long run
But confirm that the same system is activated, so you must have goals
You should set realistic goals
you want
And you can get it, maybe not so easy
If it’s simple, in a sense you already have it
This goal must push you forward, which is actually very fun
When you pursue an important goal, you want to do two things
One of them is to get this important thing
The other thing is that you become better in the pursuit
Yes
You can get both things at the same time
You have goals and at the same time increase your satisfaction with yourself
This is a very good deal
There are a lot of essential meanings in it, so the second plan
You write down your plan
On how to reach the goal and if not derail
You will also write down why this is good for you
Why is it good for your family
What might be beneficial to the community
Because you want to fix this
You have to think about the difficulties you may encounter and possible ways to overcome them in advance
And how to stay on track, all these
Because we have done a lot of research on this plan
When college students participate, they have a better start than those who don’t.
When college students participate in the program, about 25% will not withdraw
This number is pretty good
Their average academic performance has increased by about 20%
Not bad because you never know what obstacles you will encounter when you work
There are positive feelings, but not from my laboratory
Doing these things is good for your health
I think the reason may be when you look back on your autobiography
The negative emotions that have been following you can be washed away
Reduces your overall stress
Your brain calculates how dangerous the world is based on the ratio of success and failure in your life so far
Mechanism like this
Just like there are still holes on your map, you will fall into it
Your brain will still see it as a dangerous area
You prepare more for emergency actions, which is difficult
You want to go back in time and fix these experiences
These will simultaneously change the current ratio
It’s complicated, but that’s what you do
Write down what you have to write
Everything that makes you uncomfortable
Share with others
There are several reasons for doing this
One of them is that there is no other way
If i wanna do it with you
The grading load will be very high
But I think it is still worth doing, because this class is about narration and self-narration, so it should be done
Many of you will graduate soon
This is also helpful, it should be very helpful, this is from the student report
3 people will rate your homework and score, and then take the average of the two with the highest score
This will give you constructive feedback
Constructive feedback tends to support what you are doing right
Maybe some tips are about which piece you can enrich
That's it, you need to write a paper
The details are explained on the website
This is the website, click on this website, the class is on the left
Click on the class and you will see a bunch of tabs, one of which is Spirit 434, which is obviously this class
The extracurricular reading content is also listed here
And how do you pass this course
The date is not accurate, I have updated it but not yet finished
But everything else can be used
This writing plan is an online plan, it will know how you do it
But I sincerely suggest that you start this week
because
When you spend more time, the result will be better
Like a writing explosion
During the intermission period, it is your brain’s way to consolidate new knowledge
Think carefully to do this
Ask yourself
This is a different way
It’s fun when you ask yourself questions, because part of you will answer
And you don't know what the answer will be
But the answer will always appear
When I was about 6 years old I would ask myself questions, which is very important
Through some mysterious steps, memories will come to mind
Course has exam
So there are two assignments plus a paper
The thesis can be
Any questions you want to discuss related to the course
Must be related to the course
This is what you wrote
Some chance to write something
Finally there is an exam, the final exam
If you read the book and come in every class, there is no problem passing the exam
Because the exam is not complicated
Just a questionnaire of what you experienced
I did not do it at the beginning of the course
Because you need carrots and sticks because you are busy
You will also classify
Do key things, maybe some people can’t grasp the point, there will be such a result
I take this as the key or you won’t read it
Part of the reason is because it is difficult
Because the lecture notes can help you pass
This is about the course
Then we tell you some stories and try to explain its meaning
What i hope happens is
The narrative world opens the door to you
This is useful,
Got it
These questions will make you adapt better
Can also help you, usually people tell me about this course
Like telling something you already know
But they don't know they know
This makes sense, this wakes you up
You already have information on your behalf
In your actions
In process
In the structure of your intuition, this is implicit
I can make it clear what some of the hints about you are
This is what I do and it is what people usually do
If any of you experience this feeling in this class, it’s a good sign,
You may benefit from the course
If not, try again to see what happens
This is what will happen in this course
If this is what you want, from this course you can get
It’s nice to meet everyone, this class ends here